one-tvshows.eu 2013-06-24

# Privacy Policy | one-tvs.com

This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect about you at one-tvs.com (the "Website") and how we use this information. 

### Collection of your one-tvs.com Information

Your "one-tvs.com information" includes certain technical information gathered or received when you use one-tvs.com. Some of the technical information that may be collected or received includes: the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); Internet protocol address; information about the version of service from an affiliate that you used prior to registering with the service; other information about your geographic location; and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

While registering to use most of the one-tvs.com services is not required, there are a limited number of optional services (for example, comment on a tv-show) that require an "account". Registration functionality for one-tvs.com is provided by the one-tvs.com. If you choose to "Register an Account", you will need to register with and provide information to one-tvs.com. You will then obtain a Screen Name or other credential issued by one-tvs.com (collectively, "Screen Name") in order to access and use these optional services, and your Screen Name and associated services account will be subject to the one-tvs.com Terms of Service Agreement and Privacy Practices indicated in your registration process. 

### How Your one-tvs.com information is Used

Your one-tvs.com information is used: 

  * to operate and improve the websites, services and offerings available through one-tvs.com; 
  * to personalize the content provided to you; 
  * to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; 
  * to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; 
  * to conduct research about your use of one-tvs.com; and 
  * to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

Your one-tvs.com information will not be shared with third parties unless it is necessary to fulfill a request, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your one-tvs.com information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your one-tvs.com information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of one-tvs.com users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you. 

If you use our communications tools to disclose information about yourself publicly (for example, by making your screen name and/or video lists publicly available), other online users may obtain access to any information you provide. The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as a one-tvs.com user, may be accessed and disclosed in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); in other circumstances in which we believe one-tvs.com is being used in the commission of a crime; when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person; or when necessary either to protect our rights or property or the rights or property of our affiliated providers, or for us to render the service you have requested. We may use agents and contractors in order to help operate the service. If such agents and contractors have access to your one-tvs.com information, they are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for one-tvs.com. 

In the event that ownership of us or the one-tvs.com service was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your one-tvs.com information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your one-tvs.com information, we will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer. 

### Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies

Cookies are text files that are placed in your computer's browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as a one-tvs.com user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browser's settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you will not be able to take advantage of certain one-tvs.com offerings. 

We may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in combination with your one-tvs.com information to enhance and personalize your experience on one-tvs.com, including to operate and improve offerings through one-tvs.com; to help authenticate you when you use one-tvs.com; to remember your preferences; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of one-tvs.com offerings and advertisements; and, to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through one-tvs.com. 

one-tvs.com and its advertisers may use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on one-tvs.com. These advertising networks may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. Any choices that you have about these technologies will be presented here in the event we utilize the services of any advertising network provider. Therefore, you are encouraged to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks. 

### Security

We have established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your one-tvs.com information, but cannot guarantee that this information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers). 

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about one-tvs.com's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to one-tvs.com's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from one-tvs.com, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.
